dazeinfo.com 2012-06-04

# Privacy Policy l Dazeinfo

Dazeinfo.com is a Technology analysis blog which showcases amazing insights of IT Industry. Dazeinfo is committed to safeguard privacy of its users while online at Dazeinfo.com. We have right to collect information (whenever necessary) from our users like name, email address, etc. And we abide by the terms and conditions and we never share/sell any of your information to any third party authority by any means. Like most web services we keep track of visitor logs which involves information like IP address, Browser Info, Operating System Info, [Internet](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/internet/ "Internet") Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze [trends](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/trends/ "trends"), administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. This log may be used to improve service offered by us and to find copyright violators. These logs will not be made public unless required by law.

We make use of [Google](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/google/ "Google")’s services like Feedburner and other services to send [email](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/email/ "email") notification and Rss feed campaigns for to our users/readers. And we assure that such information shared with such services are never available to use for any third-party and its use is governed by privacy policy and other terms of service by those services.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

[Google](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/google/ "Google"), as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the [Internet](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/internet/ "Internet"). Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of [security](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/security/ "security") measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) [technology](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/technology/ "technology") and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social [security](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/security/ "security") numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web [browser](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/browser/ "browser") (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your [computer](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/computer/ "computer") warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party[links](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/links/ "links")**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), our policy is located at http://www.coppa.org/comply.htm.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://Dazeinfo.com/tos/](http://techgyo.com/index.php/terms-of-service)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.dazeinfo.com/[connect](http://www.dazeinfo.com/connect/ "connect")/

No 95/5, 12th Cross, 8th Main  
Wilson Garden  
Bangalore, Karnataka 560027  
India  
info@dazeinfo.com

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Dazeinfo.com does use cookies on your web browser to offer you best navigation/features Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Our sponsor advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Infolinks.

Cookies, [JavaScript](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/javascript/ "JavaScript"), or Web Beacons may also be used by the third-party authorities and ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to customize the advertising content preferences that apprears on Dazeinfo.com page.  
Since we has no access/control over these third party cookies that are used by third-party advertisers we are not liable for any loss affected by our advertisers. Dazeinfo.com privacy policy will not apply and we cannot control the preferences and activities of our sponsored advertising partners.

It is your(user’s/reader’s) responsibility to read respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out (avoid) of certain practices and these third party cookies can be blocked by the web browser and it is not mandatory to read free content from Dazeinfo.com. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web [browsers](http://dazeinfo.com/tag/browsers/ "browsers") can be found respective support websites of your web browser.

##### Incoming search terms:

  * www coppa org/comply htm
